Your power… it's monstrous.
You actually survived one hit.
Good for you.
Hah.
How do you think
I conquered half the world?
Too bad.
You still have to die.
This is not over!
Dragon Breath of the Abyss!
Divine Manifestation.
Dragon Slayer.
You think you
deserve to fight me?
Heh… you think you won?
I have Elowen’s father.
If they don’t hear from
me by nightfall, he dies.
My lord, the Black Dragon Covenant has taken my father.
They demand you come.
Tell them I’m coming.
So, my dear Godfather...
you gonna trade the supreme
Morellan family for my life?
No one threatens me.
Find the demon who took him.
Round up his entire family.
What are you doing?
None of your concern. Just die.
One more hour.
If your precious Godfather son-in-law
doesn't show up by then,
your head comes off.
The Godfather doesn’t bow to threats.
Give it up.
They say the Godfather values family above all else.
That makes you his weakness.
Anyone who touches my family dies!